Frontend Developer

Atakere Kester Williams

Objective

I'm a Frontend and Mobile App developer based in Lagos Nigeria, and i'm currently learning latest web technologies to achieve Fullstack status. I write and build with a mindset that User-Experience is most paramount in any work flow; hence the reason for my consistent immersive designs.

Experience

August 2018

Started Frontend Development

Started my web development journey set on the goal of making Web Development more known as a transformational and profitable skill through my works and impact in the development community in Nigeria and the World at large.

June 2020 - Current

Freelance Frontend developer

I offer web development services that put business in the right spot socially; getting across to the right customers and easily accessible by many.

August 2020 - Current

Mobile Development

I started mobile development using React Native in building my app , Self, which an all-in-one app for Android and iOS users.

Education

April 2018 - April 2022

BSc. Elect/Elect Engineering

Obafemi Awolowo University

Skills

Html Php/ Mysql
Js / Jquery Three Js
Css/ Scss React Native
React Js Netlify

Interests

I enjoy watching movies, gaming dancing and being a bathroom singer

Contact

Codergon

■ Codergon

O Codergon1

alphagon4@gmail.com

Codergon